plrgoldmember.com 2010-11-28

# PLR Gold Member | Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

**We Respect Your Privacy**

**100% Safe and Secure Shopping**

We understand that you want to control your personal information down to the last detail. The information you share with us goes no further and we don't think having a good shopping experience means getting pelted with loads of unsolicited "related" email from other companies after you've made your purchase. We don't like it and we won't do it.

We request information from the user on our order form. A user must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date).

This information is only used for billing purposes and to fulfil customer's orders.

If we have trouble processing an order, the information is used to contact the user (We never even see your credit card details, they are processed in real-time by our merchant PayPal)

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We use only session ID cookies. A session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates.

Once you enter your email address and customer code a cookie will be placed on your computer to remember your details ONLY on our site. By setting a cookie, users would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If you reject the cookie, you may still access our site.

**Newsletter Subscription**

If a user wishes to receive their free report and regular updates from us, we ask for contact information such as name and email addresses. Out of respect for our users privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications and will never rent out or disclose email addresses to other companies.

Users who no longer wish to receive our communications may opt-out by selecting the un-subscribe link in the email received.

**Links**

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information.
